In fact, when we are changing the version, you may not say that you can change to the ideal form at once.
And we still recommend that because you can adjust it while you can see the difference between 2D and 3D space.
So you can adjust it little by little.
It's just that you need to make a division of the board.
Some operations are divided into pieces and some are divided into sections.
This is also to make this door frame.
I'll show you how to make a door frame.
Because some of my friends say, how do you make this door frame with these pants?
I don't know how to do it.
You draw the line first.
Then use the hook outline tool to hook the area of ​​this down part out.
Then copy and paste a piece.
You can see that I will use a lot of these functions in the process of operating this software.
It's because the freezing can help you reduce the computing power of the software.
And when sewing, especially when you look at our pants.
In fact, this board is very small.
But it has a lot of layers.
When there are more layers like this,
Remember to deal with the sewing line type.
Because we are now folding this side.
This side is all folded together.
We need to change the sewing line type.
Changed to turn.
If you don't change it, there will be some conflicts in this position.
If there is such a conflict, it will be unstable.
This board is easy to wear out.
Then include these two boards.
They are also folded together.
Remember to change the sewing line type to turn.
Then close.
We put this board together.
Actually, you can immediately determine how to sew when you put it in a 3D window like me.
You can also sew in 3D space.
Then we sew it together.
Don't forget to analyze and simulate together.
That is, freezing and disassembling are a process that you need to repeat frequently during your operation.
It is a process of repeated operation.
That is, sometimes you move the board there and you don't un-move it.
Then you sew a lot of the sewing lines.
As a result, you have to output this file at the end.
Then you un-move all the boards and simulate them.
In that case, it is easy to cause instability.
Because the frozen board is frozen.
But when you create this sewing line and modify the board,
it is related to it.
Related to the frozen board.
If it has some adjustments in the grid.
For example, we change the particle diameter.
For example, we change the sewing line.
Right, right.
These are the operations.
This kind of operation will affect the grid.
It will also affect the sewing lines.
It will.
It will also affect the frozen boards.
So if you freeze a lot of boards,
you must remember to un-move each layer.
Or after a period of time,
to un-move the boards.
Let them simulate each other.
Even if you freeze the belt and un-move the pants.
And then un-move the pants.
Un-move the belt.
It's okay.
Okay, okay.
Because I just got a cold.
I have a severe cough.
Thank you, thank you.
You have to take care of your body.
Protect your body.
Don't fake it.
Fake it is very uncomfortable.
Okay.
Then let's set the position of this pocket.
I used a 3D drawing tool.
Because sometimes I have.
For example, you have no concept of this board.
I don't know where you want to add things.
You can draw some lines on 3D.
Then use it as a reference.
To set the position of the pocket you want to make.
Let's make a pocket.
You can also adjust the size.
Okay.
Then we can delete the excess 3D lines.
Draw another pocket for him.
The line with the lid sewed.
Okay.
Use the loop outline tool.
Select a line.
When double-clicking.
You can select a whole line.
Then put these.
The closed shape of the line structure.
To be hooked into the board.
Then we can use this board.
As the basis to make a pocket.
In the case of pockets.
We have also gone through specific tutorials before.
I won't talk about this in detail.
In short, we will use this board outline.
Expand and then choose five corners.
So you can make one.
A little bit like a folded box.
A pocket like a box.
Then set the diameter of the inner line.
Okay.
Then we sew the pocket to.
On the pants.
First sew the four sides.
Okay.
Then we sew the side.
After sewing.
You can simulate it.
Okay.
Then because we didn't give the inner line.
In the case of setting the folding angle.
This inner line.
It is.
It is 180 degrees flat.
It won't have a very obvious folding effect.
Then we use the folding and folding tool.
Okay.
You can see that I choose the inside first.
Then to the outside.
Inside to the outside.
Because when we use the straight line.
Its first root is.
It is.
Smaller than 180 degrees.
It is folded from the front to the outside.
Then.
The second root is.
Bigger than 180 degrees.
It is folded from the front to the inside.
Okay.
After using this folding angle.
We can see this pocket.
It is folded into a shape.
This is why we just did it.
When the outer line is expanded.
The inner line.
It is.
To be divided into two.
Expand twice.
So we can have.
Folding effect.
In fact.
These pockets.
If you look at the previous tutorial.
Is.
Have learned.
Okay.
In this case.
Just tell him.
How to do another kind of folding.
Because I.
I took a look.
There are a lot of military uniforms.
Have this shape of the pocket.
This is in our previous course.
I haven't talked about it.
We are.
He.
I will.
You can also practice.
I'm very comfortable.
Still.
So it's not too.
Okay.
I'm going to do it again.
So.
You.
After sewing, we have to remember that we will fold this board in and then turn it over, so there are two boards like this here, and then merge them.
After merging, because most of the folding in our software is to use the folding angle of the inner line, so we draw some folding lines here and then print them.
You can see that this is the pocket, if you want to make a square that protrudes out to the front, then the arrangement of our folding line is, this is a 180, this is a 0 degree, this is a 360.
Because the 0 degree is facing outwards, then the 360 degree is facing inwards, so it is such a square.
If you turn it over, that is, if you want its fold to be inside, that is, because I made this pocket at the end, let's take a look.
The structure of the pocket I made at the end is that the folded side is inside.
See?
In this way, our folding line needs to be 360 degrees and then 0 degrees.
Take a look at this folding line.
This line with 360 degrees is inside.
We can't see it from the outside, and then it's this 0 degree line.
So when we apply this folding angle to it, if you flip these two lines over, it will turn over and fold.
If you flip these two lines over, it will turn over and fold.
And then on the other side, you will repeat the direction of the location.
Because in the MT12 version, if you directly use control C and control 2, it will automatically 돌아umps
to the world workshop.
The created symmetrical plates are all based on your space coordinates.
That is, our coordinates are symmetrical to each other.
So if you fold it over like this, move it over manually.
Okay, let's sew it here.
When sewing this kind of pleats, you must pay attention when sewing manually.
We sew it left and right with two threads.
After sewing, because they are stacked together,
the type of sewing thread must also be changed to TURN.
Okay.
After we fix the pleats, we can start sewing.
First of all, we sew this long section first.
After sewing, you can see that although we have three plates here,
they only have one length after they are folded together.
So we just have to sew one section to the inner thread of this pocket.
When making pleats, you must be patient.
Because everyone is using software,
I am so skilled.
So you can do it little by little.
Don't be in a hurry.
If you are in a hurry, you may make the wrong steps.
Especially when you are making pleats in a single part.
Okay.
Hardening the pleats can make the folding effect of the pleats more obvious and stronger.
It can also help us to make such a shape more quickly.
Okay.
And then the sewing line at the top here.
The sewing line at the top here is the same as the bottom.
Left and right sewing.
After the left and right sewing, the type of sewing thread is changed to TURN.
Because they are stacked on one side and sewed together.
It's not flat sewing.
This should have been mentioned in the skill sharing.
If you are not familiar with this aspect,
you can also go and see the tutorial we did before.
Then you can also watch it.
Okay.
We have finished sewing the pleats.
Thank you for watching.
I will see you in the next video.
Bye.
So at this time, we have to change our thinking, if I give the pants, I now directly apply layer 1 to the pants, and the pocket will also be worn with the pants.
Then I may have to choose the pants version again, and then choose the pocket version, and then give them a unified layer of layer 1, which may be more troublesome to do this way.
In this case, we will directly use the negative layer of layer 2 to wear it directly to the door.
Don't forget to return to 0 after using the layer, I have explained the layer tool to you, including the frozen version, you must remember to defrost and then simulate it together.
If you don't defrost the simulation, it may not be stable, so I remind you again, don't freeze it, don't care about the version.
Remember to defrost when it's frozen.
After defrosting, let's simulate each other, apply these new changes, and then we will do the Cologne layer.
After the Cologne layer, remove the joint, and then delete the outer circle of the inner part first, so that we can do it, that is, from the outside, it has no seam allowance.
So we made two layers of pockets, and the cover of the pocket is used to sew this layer.
The outer layer is used to cover this kind of magic sticker, the inner layer of the magic sticker structure, so we will Cologne layer, then cancel the joint, and then delete the inner line of the outer layer.
Then do the pants, the pants part is that we want to do the pants to the effect of the boots.
Then, first of all, because we will finally customize the model position, so we will not put on the shoes in the beginning.
Because when we make shoes, the internal grout is a lot.
These grouts will affect the pair of pants.
And so we usually use these grouts to prevent bruises on the inner ар lucers and the inner enferace.
we usually end up sorta sip it, it is a pretty anything.
is that the bottom of the visible place is fixed to the virtual model with a fixing pin
to prevent it from having some wear and tear problems.
So what we are going to do now is to put the virtual model on the boots first.
After wearing the boots, we will probably determine the position of the pants that can be seen on the outside of the boots.
Then use a measuring tool to cut it.
The position of this cut is placed near the boot.
This tool is often not used on the measuring board,
but it is very convenient to make some horizontal or horizontal cuts with this tool.
We can use this board to make a ring-shaped inner line here.
.
Because this board will create an inner line along the contact surface with the clothing.
Then we have this inner line,
we can quickly determine that the boards below these inner lines
are the ones that we finally need to shrink to the boots.
Then we will use it to fix the virtual model function later.
So we will simplify these unseeable boards.
Let's cut and sew it.
After cutting and sewing, we will modify the width of these boards.
Try to make them close to our ankle.
Otherwise, if we use a fixing pin to fix the virtual model directly when we loosen it,
it will not necessarily fit the virtual model completely.
Just like we have done the position of the scrolls.
We have made it a very tight effect.
Then delete the excess curve points.
Straighten the pants panel.
And then I found when I put it on,
because the pants are tight here,
when it is tight, its side width is sometimes Bye.
sometimes it will shift
when the side wind line is shifted,
it will drag your pants
to produce such a slope.
So when we put it on,
especially to pay attention to this
is the crotch
sometimes we do not want
such a slanted
long-sleeved
fold
you have to look at
your crotch
crotch of the side wind line
these positions
is there any shift
like I just
we just look at this pair of pants
is not there such a very obvious slope
that it is to the outside
to rotate
its footboard
because we put the footboard
sit tight
after you sit tight
its side wind line
it will go to the flat
is that sometimes
it may turn a little bit
inside
will cause you
to have such a slope
and
so that you have such a slope
and so that you have such a slope
we adjust
is that you put the side wind line
like this
to drag inside
its side wind line
just is to the outside
we drag inside
to let him
do not produce such a obvious slope
just a whole line of slope
is not very good
and then slightly adjust
these pants size
of these
you have not heard
how no one asked a question
quickly
to ask a question
there is no one watching the live broadcast
Do not ask
here if we put hated thoughts
loose
a tight pants
for convenience
is for later
to make the ties
Hello
By the way
it says
that everyone
Please take a look at the door
Why do we have when
whether it is the chest of clothes
such as the exposure
or our model
is the front of the suit here exposed
Okay, I'm going to talk about the basics, and then the reason why this side is exposed is because we just narrowed the shrinkage, which is equivalent to changing the plate, and after changing it, it becomes a tight pants, and it will open in a position where there is no seam allowance, because the other places you are in are thinning, and you will open it if there is no seam allowance in this position, so sometimes when we are doing this crop, just like I mentioned before, callback
, don't do it too seriously, otherwise it will affect the open position like this, and it will be more troublesome if you modify it later. How to distinguish between the gold and silver images is like this. After selecting a plate with the editing logic tool, the arrow direction is the gold image, and the 90-degree angle is the silver image.
What kind of computer configuration can AMD use to be more smooth? It is a single-core CPU with better performance.
Eat CPU is bigger than eating graphics cards, and then you can't use AMD graphics cards. Try not to use AMD's CPU, although it is also compatible, but the optimization is not very good.
The results of the simulation test showed that if you have a PC fat key, you will see more than 70% of the input data in the output data.
Then, let's take a look at the workpiece.
After making a long strip, sew it on both sides and surround it with the thighs.
I still remind you that when you make this tie, you must remember that when you make a tie, you have to remember to mark a point of the edge of the andesite.
If you are using the workpiece, your eyes will be the same.
I have a lot of work to do. Then I will leave it as it is for this time.
Thank you so much, thanks, thank you so much.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
If the stretch deformation is too serious, it will definitely move to the knee here.
Then we can increase its friction coefficient a little bit.
After increasing the friction coefficient of the fabric, the fabric is not easy to slide.
It can be stuck in your thigh position and will not slide down.
Then we give it a copy-paste to the side.
Then you can make two.
After making two, we delete the sewing line and cross-sew them.
Then simulate it again.
It will pass by itself.
Then include the layer tool we used before.
You can use the layer tool.
Then it will cross this band.
Then manually adjust it.
Because we just changed the friction coefficient.
So this band will not move.
You see, it's wrong if the red one is like this.
Fortunately, we just added shrinkage to it.
It will be better to change the shrinkage later.
When you change the shrinkage, change it little by little.
Don't change it too much at once.
Otherwise, your band can't hold it.
Because your band is tight.
The band in the knee position is tight.
Then you can change the color of the fabric.
It's easy for you to distinguish.
Distinguish each part.
Okay, then the band.
If you need it to have a better constraint on the pants.
Because of our default fabric properties.
Its fascia strength is relatively low.
It's relatively easy to stretch.
So we have to give it.
Just increase its performance a little bit.
It's not easy to stretch the fabric a little bit.
So it's more obvious.
It can restrain our pants.
You can take a look.
See?
I changed the fabric properties.
After that.
It's obviously shrinked inside.
Because it's not easy to stretch.
It's going to have some constraints on the pants.
And then the frozen pants before.
Give him a chance to simulate it.
As for the pants.
We can change the shrinkage for him.
When we change the shrinkage.
There will be more wrinkles.
But you don't have to give too much shrinkage at once.
Because if we just gave it 110.
Then your crotch is loose again.
That cat-like fold is not obvious again.
So when we give it.
You just give it a little bit.
For example, the shrinkage is increased to 101 for him.
So that he can add some fabric to him.
Whether it's the front or the back.
In fact, I've been talking about pants for so long.
There's a lot of content behind.
And then we can draw him a elastic on the side.
I'm going to draw him a little bit of elasticity.
It's also to do some.
It's caused by irregular wrinkles.
The strength of the crotch is actually the same as the strength of the crotch.
The strength of the crotch refers to the stretch of the fabric on the front or the back.
The strength of the crotch is the effect of the direction of the crotch.
Are you crazy?
Didn't you see it?
Ah.
Can I suggest the end?
Have you ever seen our physical history tutorial?
Ah.
Lin Qingkong
Um.
Little friend.
What are you doing now?
Ah.
And some of you are watching the video.
You can touch your clothes now.
The fabric.
ah.
Um.
You go horizontal first.
Just pull it in the horizontal direction.
Ah.
Just pull your clothes.
He feels his stretch.
And then you're in the center.
Ah.
pull your fabric in the vertical direction
It will have its own fabric performance
Now pull your fabric diagonally with me
Pull your clothes
Have you noticed that your clothes are particularly easy to pull when you pull them diagonally?
It's not that it can be pulled completely
But it's easier to pull than horizontal or vertical direction
Feel it
This is because our fabric arrangement is either horizontal or vertical
If you turn in, it's all good
Are you watching live with your pyjamas on?
Or are you looking at live with a sweater?
Oh, go change your shirt
Don't watch our live so leisurely
I found that
Do you wear pyjamas?
and watch it at home.
Ha ha ha
Oh, well, it's supposed to be easy to pull.
If you are just
this
Um, the level is that you are wearing a more difficult-to-pull dress.
You can feel it when you wear a shirt like this.
Oh, thank you, White-Eyed Giant.
White-Eyed Giant is a light aircraft carrier, right? I remember.
Oh